Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65
- Enginemen's Press, 1959-1961 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1960: Mar. 4)
  - Item 12: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1960: Mar. 18)
  - Item 13: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.7 (1960: Apr. 1)
  - Item 14: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.8 (1960: Apr. 15)
  - Item 15: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.9 (1960: Apr. 29)
  - Item 16: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.10 (1960: May 13)
  - Item 17: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.11 (1960: May 27)
  - Item 18: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.12 (1960: June 10)
  - Item 19: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.13 (1960: June 24)
  - Item 20: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.14 (1960: July 8)
  - Item 21: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.15 (1960: July 22)
  - Item 22: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.16 (1960: Aug. 5)
  - Item 23: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.17 (1960: Aug. 19)
  - Item 24: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.18 (1960: Sept. 2)
  - Item 25: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.19 (1960: Sept. 16)
  - Item 26: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.20 (1960: Sept. 30)
  - Item 27: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.21 (1960: Oct. 14)
  - Item 28: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.22 (1960: Oct. 28)
  - Item 29: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.23 (1960: Nov. 11)
  - Item 30: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.24 (1960: Nov. 25)
  - Item 31: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.25 (1960: Dec. 9)
  - Item 32: Enginemen's Press, 1960; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.26 (1960: Dec. 23)
  - Item 33: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1961: Jan. 6)
  - Item 34: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1961: Jan. 20)
  - Item 35: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1961: Feb. 3)
  - Item 36: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1961: Feb. 17)
  - Item 37: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.5 (1961: Mar. 3)
  - Item 38: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.6 (1961: Mar. 17)
  - Item 39: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.7 (1961: Mar. 31)
  - Item 40: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.8 (1961: Apr. 14)
  - Item 41: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.9 (1961: Apr. 28)
  - Item 42: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.10 (1961: May 12)
  - Item 43: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.11 (1961: May 26)
  - Item 44: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.12 (1961: June 9)
  - Item 45: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.13 (1961: June 23)
  - Item 46: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.14 (1961: July 7)
  - Item 47: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.15 (1961: July 21)
  - Item 48: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.16 (1961: Aug. 4)
  - Item 49: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.17 (1961: Aug. 18)
  - Item 50: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.18 (1961: Sept. 1)
  - Item 51: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.19 (1961: Sept. 15)
  - Item 52: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.20 (1961: Sept. 29)
  - Item 53: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.21 (1961: Oct. 13)
  - Item 54: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.22 (1961: Oct. 27)
  - Item 55: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.23 (1961: Nov. 10)
  - Item 56: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.24 (1961: Nov. 24)
  - Item 57: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.25 (1961: Dec. 8)
  - Item 58: Enginemen's Press, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.26 (1961: Dec. 22)
- Enginemen's Press, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1962: Jan. 5)
  - Item 2: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1962: Jan. 19)
  - Item 3: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1962: Feb. 2)
  - Item 4: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1962: Feb. 16)
  - Item 5: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1962: Mar. 2)
  - Item 6: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (1962: Mar. 16)
  - Item 7: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.7 (1962: Mar. 30)
  - Item 8: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.8 (1962: Apr. 13)
  - Item 9: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.9 (1962: Apr. 27)
  - Item 10: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.11 (1962: May 25)
  - Item 11: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.12 (1962: June 8)
  - Item 12: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.13 (1962: June 22)
  - Item 13: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.14 (1962: July 6)
  - Item 14: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.15 (1962: July 20)
  - Item 15: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.16 (1962: Aug. 3)
  - Item 16: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.17 (1962: Aug. 17)
  - Item 17: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.18 (1962: Aug. 31)
  - Item 18: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.19 (1962: Sept. 14)
  - Item 19: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.20 (1962: Sept. 28)
  - Item 20: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.21 (1962: Oct. 12)
  - Item 21: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.22 (1962: Oct. 26)
  - Item 22: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.23 (1962: Nov. 9)
  - Item 23: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.24 (1962: Nov. 23)
  - Item 24: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.25 (1962: Dec. 7)
  - Item 25: Enginemen's Press, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4:no.26 (1962: Dec. 21)
  - Item 26: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1963: Jan. 4)
  - Item 27: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1963: Jan. 18)
  - Item 28: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1963: Feb. 1)
  - Item 29: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1963: Feb. 15)
  - Item 30: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.5 (1963: Mar. 1)
  - Item 31: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.6 (1963: Mar. 15)
  - Item 32: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.7 (1963: Mar. 29)
  - Item 33: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.8 (1963: Apr. 12)
  - Item 34: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.9 (1963: Apr. 26)
  - Item 35: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.10 (1963: May 10)
  - Item 36: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.11 (1963: May 24)
  - Item 37: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.12 (1963: June 7)
  - Item 38: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.13 (1963: June 21)
  - Item 39: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.14 (1963: July 5)
  - Item 40: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.15 (1963: July 19)
  - Item 41: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.16 (1963: Aug. 2)
  - Item 42: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.17 (1963: Aug. 16)
  - Item 43: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.18 (1963: Aug. 30)
  - Item 44: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.19 (1963: Sept. 13)
  - Item 45: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.20 (1963: Sept. 27)
  - Item 46: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.21 (1963: Oct. 11)
  - Item 47: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.22 (1963: Oct. 25)
  - Item 48: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.23 (1963: Nov. 8)
  - Item 49: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.24 (1963: Nov. 22)
  - Item 50: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.25 (1963: Dec. 6)
  - Item 51: Enginemen's Press, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.26 (1963: Dec. 20)
- Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1964: Jan. 3)
  - Item 2: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1964: Jan. 10)
  - Item 3: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.12 (1964: Mar. 20)
  - Item 4: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.14 (1964: Apr. 3)
  - Item 5: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.16 (1964: Apr. 17)
  - Item 6: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.18 (1964: May 1)
  - Item 7: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.20 (1964: May 15)
  - Item 8: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.21 (1964: May 22)
  - Item 9: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.22 (1964: May 29)
  - Item 10: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.23 (1964: June 5)
  - Item 11: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.26 (1964: June 26)
  - Item 12: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.28 (1964: July 10)
  - Item 13: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.29 (1964: July 17)
  - Item 14: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.30 (1964: July 24)
  - Item 15: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.32 (1964: Aug. 7)
  - Item 16: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.33 (1964: Aug. 14)
  - Item 17: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.34 (1964: Aug. 21)
  - Item 18: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.35 (1964: Aug. 28)
  - Item 19: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.36 (1964: Sept. 4)
  - Item 20: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.37 (1964: Sept. 11)
  - Item 21: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.38 (1964: Sept. 18)
  - Item 22: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.39 (1964: Sept. 25)
  - Item 23: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.40 (1964: Oct. 2)
  - Item 24: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.42 (1964: Oct. 16)
  - Item 25: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.45 (1964: Nov. 6)
  - Item 26: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.46 (1964: Nov. 13)
  - Item 27: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.47 (1964: Nov. 20)
  - Item 28: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.49 (1964: Dec. 4)
  - Item 29: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.51 (1964: Dec. 18)
  - Item 30: Enginemen's Press, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.52 (1964: Dec. 25)
- Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1965: Jan. 8)
  - Item 2: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1965: Jan. 15)
  - Item 3: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (1965: Jan. 22)
  - Item 4: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.5 (1965: Jan. 29)
  - Item 5: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.6 (1965: Feb. 5)
  - Item 6: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.7 (1965: Feb. 12)
  - Item 7: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.8 (1965: Feb. 19)
  - Item 8: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.9 (1965: Feb. 26)
  - Item 9: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.10 (1965: Mar. 5)
  - Item 10: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.11 (1965: Mar. 12)
  - Item 11: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.12 (1965: Mar. 19)
  - Item 12: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.13 (1965: Mar. 26)
  - Item 13: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.14 (1965: Apr. 2)
  - Item 14: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.15 (1965: Apr. 9)
  - Item 15: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.16 (1965: Apr. 16)
  - Item 16: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.17 (1965: Apr. 23)
  - Item 17: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.18 (1965: Apr. 30)
  - Item 18: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.19 (1965: May 7)
  - Item 19: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.20 (1965: May 14)
  - Item 20: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.21 (1965: May 21)
  - Item 21: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.22 (1965: May 28)
  - Item 22: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.23 (1965: June 4)
  - Item 23: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.24 (1965: June 11)
  - Item 24: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.25 (1965: June 18)
  - Item 25: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.26 (1965: June 25)
  - Item 26: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.27 (1965: July 2)
  - Item 27: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.28/29 (1965: July 6)
  - Item 28: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.30 (1965: July 30)
  - Item 29: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.31 (1965: Aug. 6)
  - Item 30: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.32 (1965: Aug. 13)
  - Item 31: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.33 (1965: Aug. 20)
  - Item 32: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.34 (1965: Aug. 27)
  - Item 33: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.35 (1965: Sept. 3)
  - Item 34: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.36 (1965: Sept. 17)
  - Item 35: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.37 (1965: Sept. 24)
  - Item 36: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.38 (1965: Oct. 1)
  - Item 37: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.39 (1965: Oct. 8)
  - Item 38: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.40 (1965: Oct. 15)
  - Item 39: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.41 (1965: Oct. 22)
  - Item 40: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.42 (1965: Oct. 29)
  - Item 41: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.43 (1965: Nov. 5)
  - Item 42: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.44 (1965: Nov. 12)
  - Item 43: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.45 (1965: Nov. 19)
  - Item 44: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.46 (1965: Dec. 3)
  - Item 45: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.47 (1965: Dec. 10)
  - Item 46: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.48 (1965: Dec. 17)
  - Item 47: Enginemen's Press, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.49 (1965: Dec. 31)
- Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1966: Jan. 7)
  - Item 2: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1966: Jan. 14)
  - Item 3: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1966: Jan. 21)
  - Item 4: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (1966: Jan. 28)
  - Item 5: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.5 (1966: Feb. 4)
  - Item 6: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.6 (1966: Feb. 11)
  - Item 7: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.7 (1966: Feb. 18)
  - Item 8: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.8 (1966: Feb. 25)
  - Item 9: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.9 (1966: Mar. 4)
  - Item 10: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.10 (1966: Mar. 11)
  - Item 11: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.11 (1966: Mar. 18)
  - Item 12: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.12 (1966: Mar. 25)
  - Item 13: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.13 (1966: Apr. 1)
  - Item 14: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.14 (1966: Apr. 8)
  - Item 15: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.15 (1966: Apr. 15)
  - Item 16: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.16 (1966: Apr. 22)
  - Item 17: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.17 (1966: Apr. 29)
  - Item 18: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.18 (1966: May 6)
  - Item 19: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.19 (1966: May 13)
  - Item 20: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.20 (1966: May 20)
  - Item 21: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.21 (1966: May 27)
  - Item 22: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.22 (1966: June 3)
  - Item 23: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.23 (1966: June 10)
  - Item 24: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.24 (1966: June 17)
  - Item 25: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.25 (1966: June 24)
  - Item 26: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.26 (1966: June 31)
  - Item 27: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.27 (1966: July 15)
  - Item 28: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.28 (1966: July 22)
  - Item 29: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.29 (1966: July 29)
  - Item 30: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.30 (1966: Aug. 3)
  - Item 31: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.31 (1966: Aug. 12)
  - Item 32: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.32 (1966: Aug. 19)
  - Item 33: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.33 (1966: Aug. 26)
  - Item 34: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.34 (1966: Sept. 2)
  - Item 35: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.35 (1966: Sept. 16)
  - Item 36: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.36 (1966: Sept. 23)
  - Item 37: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.37 (1966: Sept. 30)
  - Item 38: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.38 (1966: Oct. 7)
  - Item 39: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.39 (1966: Oct. 14)
  - Item 40: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.40 (1966: Oct. 21)
  - Item 41: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.41 (1966: Oct. 28)
  - Item 42: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.42 (1966: Nov. 4)
  - Item 43: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.43 (1966: Nov. 11)
  - Item 44: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.44 (1966: Nov. 18)
  - Item 45: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.45 (1966: Dec. 2)
  - Item 46: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.46 (1966: Dec. 9)
  - Item 47: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.47 (1966: Dec. 16)
  - Item 48: Enginemen's Press, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.48 (1966: Dec. 23)